# lê Duy Khánh

2000-03-25

Chương Mỹ, Hà Nội



## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Become an expert in the field of programming Towards developing business based on technology

## **OVERVIEW OF EXPERIENCE**

Due to my experience working for a product company with a relatively large and complex system, I have strong skills in system optimization. Additionally, I have a good ability to analyze system design from business analysis to relatively good system design, especially in building systems based on microservices architecture, and applying flexible patterns such as CQRS, saga, event sourcing. I also apply design patterns such as repository and factory effectively in programming.

## **EDUCATION**

2018 - 2023

#### INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

**Hanoi Architectural University** 

Information Technology Engineer

#### 2KILL2

- Nearly 3 years of programming experience
- Basic English communication and document reading comprehension

## SPECIALIZED KNOWLEDGE

## **Programming languages**

• C# (Primary programming language), C++, Java, Php, JS, TS, Html. . . .

#### **Frameworks**

• Asp.net core web api, asp.net mvc. . .

Ahn framework net zero asp net hollernlate

- · winform, wpf
- ReactJs, Angular, Vuejs

Optimizing system performance

· System design analysis

Quick adoption of new technologies, fast and efficient work

riop maniemoni, mot zono, aspiniot sono piato

## Database

- Sql Server
- MySql
- MongoDb
- DynamoDb•
- MariaDb
- Redis (cache)....

## Other technologies

- · IdentityServer4
- RabbitMQ, Kafka, Event bridge
- Docker
- JWT token
- · Api gateway
- AWS EC2, AWS S3, AWS Simple Queue Service, AWS Cognito

. . . . .

## Software designs/architectures

- · Micro service
- Domain-driven-design
- · Event-driven
- · Repository design patern
- Factory design partern . . . .

· System thinking, programming mindset

Deep understanding of programming languages and technologies used

• Experience in working with Agile Scrum

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Orenda

6/2020 - 9/2021

# 30shine

9/2021 - now

## **BACKEND + FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

- Discussing database design analysis for the project
- Code
- Reviewing and optimizing upgrades for the company's product project
- Exploring new technologies and implementing them into the project
- Support other teams to complete projects on time

## **BACKEND + FRONTEND DEVELOPER**

- Discuss and propose solutions based on business requirements
- Building modules to meet the operational requirements of the system
- Review, upgrade and optimize low-performance modules
- Researching new technologies to upgrade the existing system technologies
- Building a system based on microservice architecture
- Re-architecting legacy modules for the project
- Developing modules based on Domain-driven-design/ event-driven
- Build base project code
- · Hand over architecture design
- Guide others to join the project
- Experienced in working with agile scrum software development methodology
- SOLID

# Hệ thống quản lý phòng khám VCLINIC

Time - ~ 2 month

#### Client

The company's product was deployed for various clients, such as Phuong Dong Hospital, University Medical Center. . . .

Number of participants: 10

## Viện dinh dưỡng quốc gia

Time - ~ 3 month

Client: Viện dinh dưỡng quốc gia

Number of participants: 7

# Hệ thống quản lý dữ liệu tiên chủng quốc gia

Time - ~ 4 - 5 month

**Client** government

Number of participants: 8

## **POSITION DEVELOPER**

- Discuss and provide insights for analyzing and designing a normalized database based on the business requirements
- Discuss and provide opinions on the data flow within the system
- Write backend code for the system using ASP.NET and .NET Zero
- Coding the frontend of the system using Angular
- · Support colleagues to meet project deadlines

#### **TECHNOLOGY USED**

- · Asp.net web api
- · .Net zero,
- Angular,
- MySql
- MariaDb. . . . .

## **POSITION DEVELOPER**

- Analyze and design the database for some modules
- · Normalize database
- Build code flow, build base project for some modules
- Write backend code for the system using ASP.NET and .NET Zero
- Coding the frontend of the system using Angular

#### **TECHNOLOGY USED**

- · Asp.net web api
- .Net zero,
- · Angular,
- MySql
- MariaDb. . . . .

## **POSITION DEVELOPER**

- Build code flow, build base project for some modules
- Write backend code for the system using ASP.NET and ABP Framework
- · Coding the frontend of the system using Angular
- Research technology to apply to certain special parts
- Optimize complex processing parts
- Optimize data queries

#### **TECHNOLOGY USED**

- ASP.net web api
- ABP framework
- Angular
- Sql server
- MySql
- MongoDb
- Elastic Search

## Cổng đăng ký tiêm chủng MEBOO

Time - ~ 2 month

**Client** The company's product

Number of participants: 5

## 30Shine ERP system

Time - N/A

## System includes:

Booking system, mobile app for reception, mobile app for stylist, mobile app for skinner, mobile app for salon manager, hotline app for customer care staff, checkout system for salon, customer infomation management system, time attendance system, monitoring system, facilities management system, statistic, configuration system such as config product, service, salary, promotion, . . .

Number of participants: 12

#### POSITION DEVELOPER

- Analyze and design the database, normalize it based on the provided business requirements
- · Design and build data flow in the system
- Write backend code for the system using ASP.NET and ASP.NET Boilerplate
- · Coding the frontend of the system using Angular
- Research technology
- · Optimize for complex processing parts

## **TECHNOLOGY USED**

- · ASP.net web api
- ASP.NET Boilerplate
- Angular
- Sql server

## **POSITION DEVELOPER**

- Discussing and providing feedback on the system's business operations
- Design the database for the system
- Code backend + frontend
- · Research technology to optimize and upgrade the system
- Upgrade the system's technology version
- Research and implement microservice architecture with domain-driven design and event-driven design in the system
- Research technologies to apply to microservice architecture, such as event store and queue.
- Research and implement CQRS, Saga, Event sourcing. . . . .
- Research solutions to separate the database to meet the requirements of microservice architecture
- Rebuild the base of old projects according to design patterns
- Write libraries for reusability
- Research and implement Google Authenticator's 2FA security code
- Research the application of message queue technology to optimize the computing of aggregation within the system
- Optimize data read and write operations for heavy-load and potentially timeout-prone transactions
- Provide solutions for complex requirements
- Research and implement solutions for granular API authorization for each user
- Research and implement the migration of the system's business flow to use NoSQL
- Build end-of-day aggregation processes (such as reports, salaries, etc.
- Build the core for process message manager. . . . .
- · Research and implement clean architecture

## **TECHNOLOGY USED**

- · ASP.net web api
- Reactjs
- Vuejs

- Sql server
- MongoDb
- DynamoDb (aws)
- Redis
- Message Queue. . . .

## **HOBBIES**

- Music
- Game
- Art
- Reading book

# **MORE INFORMATION**

Besides working on projects and software systems for companies, I have also worked on many outsourced software systems related to e-commerce, auction, and pharmaceuticals.

© topcv.vn